whatisdibi.com 2011-08-12

# Privacy Policy | DIBI

### Cookies, IP addresses and statistics

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. A form of login or user account is used for this website but not always necessary, cookies should be enabled to use this feature. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a numerical identification that your computer or other browsing device sends out. We use cookies and IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Cookies and IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Secure storage

All of our registrants’ information is restricted in our office. Only members of our team who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. No sponsors, speakers or supporters will have access to personal details.

### Sharing

Codeworks or DIBI Conference will not, under any circumstances, share with any third party individual IP addresses, email addresses, personal contact details or other information collected through this website or related statistic tracking systems. If information sharing is required for the purposes of this or any other event, you will be given immediate notice.

### External links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.

### Data Protection

As we are not classed as a “data controller”, we do not have to notify the Information Commissioner about the information we collect or our practices. Please note however, that we comply meticulously with the eight principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 and understand best practice for managing information.

### Questions

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can [email Gavin](mailto:gavin.elliott@codeworks.net "Email Gavin").
